grouptable.com 2014-10-19

# Bangalore Restaurants | Online Restaurant Booking | Table Reservations for Restaurants in Bangalore - GroupTable

**1.1**  General. ValueNet Ecommerce Pvt Ltd ("ValueNet", "GroupTable.com", or "we", "our" or "us") takes very seriously the private nature of your personally identifying information. The privacy of all GroupTable users is very important. This Privacy Policy describes how we use the information we obtain when you visit[](https://www.grouptable.com/) (the "Site") or use the products & services offered through the Site (collectively, the "Services"). Please read this notice carefully and do not hesitate to let us know if you have any questions.

 **1.2**  Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy. By using or accessing the Site, you are acknowledging and accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please note that we may update this Privacy Policy as we change or develop the Site or Services. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your acceptance of the then-current Privacy Policy. For this reason, we recommend that you review the Privacy Policy from time to time to ensure that you understand and are willing to accept the current privacy practices of GroupTable.com.

Section 2. How We Use Your Private Information

 **2.1**  Email Address and Mobile Number. When you sign up for a GroupTable.com account, or other service or promotion that requires registration, you will be required to provide a valid email address and/or a mobile number. We will use the provided email address and/or mobile number to contact you as part of the transaction process, to send you periodic alerts that you have subscribed to, or for purposes that are intended to enhance your user experience. We may also contact you to obtain feedback on merchant offers in which you have participated or utilized.

We will also share your mobile number with the merchant/restaurant owner when you purchase an offer or book a table at the merchant’s establishment. This is necessary to ensure a smoother redemption of the offer and to facilitate a pleasant dining experience for you. We will not share your contact information with any other third parties, except as provided in Section 6.1. GroupTable.com will generally ask you to indicate whether or not you want to receive certain types of email/SMS communication from us, and we will adhere to your preferences unless we consider a particular communication to be absolutely necessary.

 **2.2**  Name. When purchasing a GroupTable Offer, you may be required to provide the full name of the person who will use it, whether that will be you or the person to whom you plan to transfer the GroupTable Offer. We will only share this name with the merchant listed on that GroupTable Certificate. Your full name may be used by the merchant for the purposes of verifying that the GroupTable Certificate is valid. We will also collect your full name during the checkout process to verify your credit card payment information. When signing up for a GroupTable.com account, or other services or promotions that require registration, you may also be asked to provide your name at that time so that we can personalize all communications you receive from us.

 **2.3**  Financial Information. For certain services, such as our merchant offers, we also request credit card or other payment account information which are maintained by our payment processor in encrypted form on secure servers. We do not share this information with any third party except the companies responsible for processing our credit card transactions.

 **2.4**  Demographic Information. We will occasionally collect demographic data, such as, gender and occupation. Providing this information is typically optional but helps us bring you better deals. We use this data to help determine which deals our users would most appreciate. We may also share this data with third parties, such as merchants featured on our site; however, no third party will be able to trace your personal demographic information back to you unless you have separately given your permission to do so.

 **2.5**  Information Collected from Third Parties. We may combine information you submit under your account with information from other services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

 **2.5.1**  Facebook. By logging into the Site using your Facebook credentials, you will be giving GroupTable.com or the third party service provider access to certain general personally identifying information stored in your Facebook profile. We will not view or store any data available to us from your Facebook profile without first obtaining your consent. You will be able to select what information we and/or the third party service provider obtain from Facebook when registering for your GroupTable.com account nad/or related services/promotions. At various times on GroupTable.com, you will be able to share our content with your Facebook friends. We do not view or store lists of your friends, nor do we view or store the specific messages that you send to your friends. However, we may record the number of times that particular content has been shared.

Section 3. Sharing functionality

 **3.1**  At various times, you will be able to share content on our site using the share feature. We do not view or store the specific messages that you send through this feature, but we may record the number of times that particular content has been shared.

Section 4. Cookies, GIF Images and Unique URLs

 **4.1**  Cookies. Like most sites, GroupTable.com makes use of browser "cookies". Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. GroupTable.com does not use cookies to retrieve or track information that is unrelated to the Site or services.

 **4.2**  Unique URLs. GroupTable.com may also create unique links in emails that enable us to track on which emails you click.

Section 5. Your IP Address

 **5.1**  We collect and store your IP address. This helps us diagnose problems with our servers, administer our site, gather non-personally identifying information about our users, and detect and prevent fraudulent activity.

Section 6. Information sharing

 **6.1**  GroupTable.com only shares your personally identifying information with other companies or individuals, outside of ValueNet in, in limited circumstances.

 **6.1.1**  Except as provided in Section 6.1.2, we require your consent before we share any of your personally identifying information.

 **6.1.2**  Disclosure to Third Parties.

 **6.1.2.1**  We may provide personally identifying information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf.

 **6.1.2.2**  We reserve the right to transfer or assign the personally identifying information we have collected from you in the event GroupTable.com is acquired by, or merges into, a third party, or in the event we undergo any other form of reorganization. In certain limited circumstances, our business partners may have a contractual right to obtain a copy of your contact information and to contact you if GroupTable.com is unable to fulfil our contractual obligations to those parties.

 **6.1.2.3**  We may share your personally identifying information when we believe in good faith that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of GroupTable.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

Section 7. Usage Information

 **7.1**  GroupTable.com may also collect non-personally identifying, aggregated information about subscribers for use of our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how visitors to our site use our service. For example, we may view how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites users came, and which links to external sites have been used, among other things. We may share this data with third parties in an aggregated, non- personally identifying form. Such information does not identify you individually.

Section 8. How to access and update your personal information

 **8.1**  Although we take reasonable steps to ensure that all data we use is accurate, we depend on our users to update or correct their personally identifying information whenever necessary. We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personally identifying information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.

Section 9. Minors

 **9.1**  GroupTable.com does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If we determine that any content has been uploaded to the Site by someone under the age of 13, it will be removed. If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, please ask your parent's permission before using the Site and the Service. Some Offers may be subject to further age limitations.

Section 10. Links to other websites

 **10.1**  The Site may contain links to other websites. GroupTable.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of third parties or the content of these websites. If you follow these links you are responsible for reviewing the privacy policy of any third party website to determine that your personally identifying information is protected to your satisfaction.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website by clicking the "contact us" link.
